#### Contact

tina205nurse@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tinag-18922720 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Research
Wound Care
Healthcare Management

# **Tina Goodin Hill**

Registered Nurse and Travel Agent at Goodin Global Travel United States

## Summary

Im a per diem strike and travel nurse, in pursuit of a position that allows me to implement the skills and knowledge that I possess while gaining new experiences. I'm also an Independent Travel agent able to meet your travel needs, whether great or small.

## Experience

Goodin Global Travel Travel Agent March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months) Birmingham, Alabama Area

Servicing all your travel needs, in the U.S. or abroad. Goodinhilltravel@yahoo.com

Fastaff Travel Nursing
Travel RN
February 2011 - Present (9 years 5 months)

Fresenius Medical Care
Registered Nurse
November 2010 - Present (9 years 8 months)

Fresenius Medical Care North America Clinic Manager November 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 8 months)

st vincents hospital 7 years 3 months

Registered Nurse June 2006 - August 2009 (3 years 3 months)

Float to various med surg, telemetry and observation units

Staff RN

June 2002 - August 2006 (4 years 3 months)

Page 1 of 2

2002-Staff nurse on cardiac unit 2005- float pool nurse

# Education

A H Parker High School